{
    "subject": "resource/2012_UniCredit_Czech_Open_\u2013_Doubles",
    "predicate": "property/rd2Team",
    "object": "A Men\u00e9ndez",
    "human_readable": "The rd2 team of 2012 UniCredit Czech Open \u2013 Doubles is A Men\u00e9ndez.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.978914737701416,
            "question": "Who is on the rd2 team of 2012 UniCredit Czech Open \u2013 Doubles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9497542977333069,
            "question": "What year did A Men\u00e9ndez play in the UniCredit Czech Open \u2013 Doubles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8776761293411255,
            "question": "What is A Men\u00e9ndez's role on the rd2 team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8235193490982056,
            "question": "Where was the UniCredit Czech Open \u2013 Doubles held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8167895078659058,
            "question": "Was A Men\u00e9ndez part of a singles or doubles team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6175026297569275,
            "question": "In what type of competition was A Men\u00e9ndez playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.545655369758606,
            "question": "What was the name of the tournament A Men\u00e9ndez participated in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4815468192100525,
            "question": "Who else is on the rd2 team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08685439825057983,
            "question": "Is there information about the team's performance in the tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.050341151654720306,
            "question": "What is the name of the competition organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The rd2 team of 2012 UniCredit Czech Open \u2013 Doubles is A Men\u00e9ndez.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1276_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there information about the team's performance in the tournament?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1276_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who else is on the rd2 team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1276_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the tournament A Men\u00e9ndez participated in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1276_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1276_32.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe document does not mention that Adrian Menendez-Maceiras, also referred to as Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez, was part of the rd2 team of the 2012 UniCredit Czech Open - Doubles. The document only mentions him as a player who received entry from the qualifying draw and a doubles champion in the 2011 UniCredit Czech Open."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez participated in the 2011 UniCredit Czech Open as a wildcard entrant and reached the doubles final with Sergei Bubka. However, there is no information supporting that his name appears in the title of the doubles team for the 2012 edition of the same tournament."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez was a participant in the 2012 UniCredit Czech Open singles tournament, but not the doubles. His doubles partner Sergei Bubka is incorrectly identified as A Men\u00e9ndez in the provided information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information about the UniCredit Czech Open from 2011 states that Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez won the doubles title with Sergei Bubka.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The 2012 UniCredit Czech Open was not mentioned anywhere in the provided context information, but the 2011 edition of the same tournament was mentioned, and its doubles champions were listed as Sergei Bubka / Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not list Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez as part of any doubles team for the 2012 UniCredit Czech Open. Instead, it mentions Adri\u00e1n Men\u00e9ndez as one of the players who received entry from the qualifying draw, and later pairs him with Sergei Bubka as champions in the doubles event for the 2011 UniCredit Czech Open, not 2012.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}